

NGO VAN TRUNG

+84 94 612 9294 | trung2601.it@gmail.com | github.com/TrungNgoVan

ABOUT ME

I'm Trung, a third-year Mathematics and Computer Science major at VNUHCM - University Of Science. I'm passionate about programming and technology. I have experience working on several real projects. I am particularly interested in becoming a Backend Developer. I have strong self-study and time management skills to help me achieve this goal.

EDUCATION

BSC IN COMPUTER SCIENCE & MATHEMATICS University of Science, VNU-HCM | GPA: 7.5/10 (3.2/4)

SKILLS

Programming:

- Language: C/C++, JavaScript, Python, Go
 Knowledge: OOP, DSA, Database, Network
- Database: MongoDB, MySQL, Redis
- Project versioning: Git
- API development: Postman, Insomnia

Other:

- Communication
- Leadership

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- 2023
 - o Top 20 GDSC HACKATHON VIETNAM 2023 (Role Backend)
- 2022
 - Top 238 Shopee Code League.
 - o Top 5 HCMUS Student Competition with ASEAN Information Security
 - Top 10 mentor YOUPRENEUR LAUNCHPAD 2022.
- 2021
 - Champion "Đi tìm thủ lĩnh HCMUS 2021"
- 2018
 - o Silver medal at the Informatics Olympiad in Dak Lak province.

WORK EXPERIENCE

BACKEND INTERN

Approi Ltd. Growth Marketing Agency
 | 09/2023 - Now

BACKEND DEVELOPER

Google Developer Student Clubs Chapter HCMUS
 12/2022 - Now

MENTOR

- Mentor 2 startup projects in Youpreneur Launchpad 2022.
- Support ideas, technology tools for project implementation

| 5/2022 - 8/2022

TEACHING ASSISTANT

- Kmin Academy Học viện khoa học máy tính
- Basic Javascript, C++, Typescript classes

| 2/2022 - 8/2023

MEMBER

- PiMA Projects in Mathematics and Applications
- Contribute an article about "Dynamic programming" on fanpage

| 9/2021 - 3/2023

PROJECTS

Project Student Manager System

- Use C++, knowledge of OOP and data structure.
- Basic CRUD app for managing students' info in universities

Project Authentication API

- Use ExpressJS, MongoDB
- Use JWT authentication for user authentication and authorization.
- Use Bcryptjs for password encoding and decoding

Blog "Sổ tay của Henry"

- Built with Hugo.
- . Blog about my algorithm, technology, experience in the field of programming

Morning Basket

- Role: Backend NodeJS (main)
- Use Javascript, ReactJS, MongoDB
- Use knowledge of authenticate, database, design e-commerce API.